<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Cambridge UK</string>

    <string name="category_spots_places">Spots &amp; Places</string>
    <string name="category_food_drink">Food &amp; Drink</string>
    <string name="category_hotels">Hotels</string>
    <string name="category_shopping">Shopping</string>

    <string name="spots_places_title_computing">The Centre for Computing History</string>
    <string name="spots_places_title_university">University of Cambridge</string>
    <string name="spots_places_title_rivercam">The River Cam</string>
    <string name="spots_places_title_fitzwilliam">Fitzwilliam Museum</string>
    <string name="spots_places_title_botanic">Cambridge University Botanic Garden</string>

    <string name="food_drink_title_signorelli">Signorelli\'s Deli Cambridge</string>
    <string name="food_drink_title_ilpiccolomondo">Ristorante Il Piccolo Mondo</string>
    <string name="food_drink_title_trinity">Trinity Restaurant</string>
    <string name="food_drink_title_breadmeat"><![CDATA[Bread & Meat]]></string>
    <string name="food_drink_title_africfood">Africfood</string>

    <string name="hotels_title_ibis">Ibis Cambridge Central Station</string>
    <string name="hotels_title_anstey">Anstey Hall</string>
    <string name="hotels_title_holidayinn">Holiday Inn Express Cambridge</string>
    <string name="hotels_title_quymill"><![CDATA[Quy Mill Hotel & Spa]]></string>
    <string name="hotels_title_travelodge">Travelodge</string>

    <string name="shopping_title_grafton">The Grafton</string>
    <string name="shopping_title_arcade">Grand Arcade</string>
    <string name="shopping_title_lionyard">Lion Yard Shopping Centre</string>
    <string name="shopping_title_bookshop">Cambridge University Press Bookshop</string>
    <string name="shopping_title_tattooing">Custom Ink Tattooing</string>

    <string name="spots_places_computing_descr">The Centre for Computing History is a hands-on interactive display of computers and game consoles that date back to the early sixties! From Pong to Pokémon, experience game play evolving. The display includes the huge computers of the sixties, the home computers of the 80’s and much more.</string>
    <string name="spots_places_university_descr">Founded in 1209, nearly a century after Oxford University was established, the university was formally incorporated in 1571 and was patterned after those of Oxford and Paris with a traditional course of study based on Latin grammar, rhetoric and logic, arithmetic, geometry, music and astronomy..</string>
    <string name="spots_places_camriver_descr">Punting along the River Cam is a must when visiting Cambridge. Beautiful scenes along the river that you only get to see when punting. I recommend a touring punt instead of a self-punt so you can enjoy the interesting facts about Cambridge surroundings. And keep an eye out for the Pimms Punt!</string>
    <string name="spots_places_fitzwilliam_descr">Museum houses vast collections of antiquities from ancient Egypt, Greece and Rome, including exhibits of English and European pottery and glass, furniture, clocks, Chinese jades, and ceramics from Japan and Korea.</string>
    <string name="spots_places_botanic_descr">This heritage-listed Botanic Garden was originally conceived by Professor John Henslow, the mentor and teacher of Charles Darwin. The Garden\'s plant collections today number over 8000 species from all over the world, displayed within the best collection of trees in the region. The 40 acres of beautifully-landscaped gardens and glasshouses offer year-round interest and seasonal inspiration. The excellent Cafe and Shop are also open year-round. An oasis in the City, this great Garden makes a great day out.</string>

    <string name="food_drink_signorelli_descr">Our in-house bakery offers freshly made pizzas, bread and most importantly our famous Pasticcini. We also have a large selection of Italian cured meats and cheeses from small independent farms. Our additional wine corner offers consumers a chance to taste, drink and purchase our fine wines selection as well as our Italian craft beer.</string>
    <string name="food_drink_ilpiccolomondo_descr">Il Piccolo Mondo – or ‘The Small World’ – in Bottisham is a delightful 45 cover authentic Italian restaurant that maintains many of the original features of its historic building.</string>
    <string name="food_drink_trinity_descr">Independent British restaurant offering quality freshly prepared and cooked food with excellent service. Menu biased towards fresh fish with meat,Vegetarian and Gluten Free options.</string>
    <string name="food_drink_breadmeat_descr">Independent Cambridge eatery. Straightforward, unfussy menu is far from ordinary, hot roast meat sandwiches top the bill, alongside soups and salads all cooked on-site with the best of ingredients, ethically and locally sourced. A relaxed atmosphere awaits, where you can enjoy our favourite beers, wines, fresh coffee and tea.</string>
    <string name="food_drink_africfood_descr">We offer African food at the Cambridge Market.</string>

    <string name="hotels_ibis_descr">Ibis Cambridge is located next to the train station and a 10 min walk to the city centre. Each of the 231 modern guest rooms has Freeview TV, tea and coffee making facilities and the Sweetbed by ibis. Enjoy our Coffee shop and Bar. The hotel provides free high-speed Wi-Fi throughout. Breakfast available 4am to 12 noon. Hot and continental breakfast selection from 6:30am to 10am. Free on-site cycle park and nearby car park (paying). No smoking.</string>
    <string name="hotels_anstey_descr">Our bed and breakfast acommodation features:- Huge bedrooms, some with four poster beds.- Beautiful antique furniture and a world class collection of Post Impressionist paintings all around you.- Bathrooms with massive roll-top baths or modern wet room showers.- Tea and coffee making in each room.- An honour bar with a well stocked collection of drinks.- Free wi-fi throughout.- Modern TVs in every room.</string>
    <string name="hotels_holidayinn_descr">Enjoy a peaceful stay at the modern Holiday Inn Express Cambridge hotel, just 2 miles from Cambridge city centre. Guests can enjoy free Wi-Fi, well-equipped bedrooms with comfort cooling and free onsite parking. An inclusive Express Start buffet breakfast with hot items is included for all guests. Host a presentation in one of Holiday Inn Express Cambridge\'s 3 naturally lit meeting rooms, all with free Wi-Fi. We\'re easy for your delegates to reach, just 24 miles from Stansted Airport on the M11 and 1.5 miles from Cambridge train station. It\'s just a short walk from the hotel to meetings with companies based in Coldhams Business Park. Cambridge's focal point is its beautiful university campus, packed with medieval college buildings and the Gothic King's College Chapel. Sail along the tranquil River Cam by punt for a city tour with a difference, passing picturesque parks and beautiful bridges. Order dinner and drinks at the hotel's bar and relax in the Great Room lounge.</string>
    <string name="hotels_quymill_descr">Whatever you expect from a four star luxurious small hotel in Cambridge, you will be pleasantly surprised by the Quy Mill Hotel &amp; Spa! Once an historic watermill, Quy Mill Hotel &amp; Spa is a secluded haven which offers charming hotel accommodation in Cambridge, award winning 2 AA Rosette food and unfailing courtesy. It has long been a magnet for visitors from across the world, and they come here to Cambridge for a great many reasons. Guests enjoy the University City of Cambridge, and the easy access to Newmarket and the range of treasures to be found in the area. They appreciate the peaceful atmosphere, the excellent food and the attentive service of the Mill. We often welcome back couples who were married here so they can remember the enchantment of their Cambridge wedding. Our business clients comment on the ease with which any arrangements can be made and how they look forward to a session in our Health Club when the day\'s business is concluded - available free to guests, it is complete with a stunning deck level pool. Our business clients recall the enjoyment and benefit of corporate team building exercise in our famous 'five acre field' and Quy Mill Hotel &amp; Spa has become their first port of call when looking for places to stay in Cambridge. All our rooms feature en-suite bath and shower and some offer the height of exclusivity with four poster beds and double whirlpool spa baths. Our award-winning restaurant will create a tempting selection of local and international dishes, while room service is on call 24 hours a day. A full list of amenities can be reached here. Welcome to Quy Mill Hotel &amp; Spa. We promise to provide everything you would expect from a luxury hotel in Cambridge - and much much more!</string>
    <string name="hotels_travelodge_descr">Our Cambridge Newmarket Road hotel is just over a mile away from one of the UK’s most popular cities. Admire stunning architecture dating back hundreds of years and explore some world-class museums on foot.
For shopaholics, Cambridge has plenty of stores and boutiques packed into its centre, while there’s an abundance of galleries, including the Fitzwilliam Museum, to enjoy – and that’s all in addition to beautiful university buildings such as Christ’s College.
All rooms feature a comfy king size bed with four plump pillows and a cosy duvet. Our on-site restaurant and bar serves breakfast and tasty evening meals.</string>

    <string name="shopping_grafton_descr">The Centre is open 7 days a week with late night shopping every Wednesday to 8pm with ample on-site parking, and plenty of local buses stopping at The Grafton bus interchange. You can also get here on the including the park &amp; ride service.
To make your trip easy and comfortable there are cash points, baby changing facilities, an information point, first aid, security, toilets, cycle racks and a shopmobility scheme with wheelchair hire.</string>
    <string name="shopping_arcade_descr">Grand Arcade is surrounded by historic Cambridge, and is easily combined with a trip to visit these beautiful world-renowned tourist destinations. The mall is easily accessible by car, bike and public transport. Park for just £1 every day after 5pm in our multi-storey carpark which includes shopmobility facilities and a 500-space cycle park. We are conveniently situated near to the city centre stops for the Park &amp; Ride and the Guided Bus services, and is only a short walk from Cambridge Train Station.</string>
    <string name="shopping_lionyard_descr">Lion Yard is a modern shopping centre in the heart of the city. With over 40 stores to choose from, you are always only a few steps away from that perfect purchase.
The shopping centre comprises of two spacious floors, housed underneath a beautiful glass roof. There are three main entrances to the Lion Yard's central atrium, Petty Cury, St Andrews and Market Square</string>
    <string name="shopping_bookshop_descr">The Cambridge University Press Bookshop is the oldest bookshop site in the country. Books have been sold here since at least 1581. We are proud to house the best of Cambridge publishing - from Art to Zoology, you will find something to interest and amaze.</string>
    <string name="shopping_tattooing_descr">We are Custom Ink Tattooing based in Cambridge, and we specialise in custom tattoo work!</string>
</resources>
