<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Know Berlin</string>

    <string name="category_spots_places">Spots &amp; Places</string>
    <string name="category_food_drink">Food &amp; Drink</string>
    <string name="category_hotels">Hotels</string>
    <string name="category_shopping">Shopping</string>

    <string name="spots_places_reichstag_desc">The Reichstag is a historic edifice in Berlin, Germany, constructed to house the Imperial Diet of the German Empire. It was opened in 1894 and housed the Diet until 1933, when it was severely damaged after being set on fire. After World War II, the building fell into disuse; the parliament of the German Democratic Republic met in the Palast der Republik in East Berlin, while the parliament of the Federal Republic of Germany met in the Bundeshaus in Bonn.</string>
    <string name="spots_places_cathedral_desc">The Berlin Cathedral is the short name for the Evangelical Supreme Parish and Collegiate Church in Berlin, Germany. It is located on Museum Island in the Mitte borough. The current building was finished in 1905 and is a main work of Historicist architecture of the "Kaiserzeit".</string>
    <string name="spots_places_fernsehturm_desc">The Fernsehturm (English: Television Tower) is a television tower in central Berlin, Germany. Close to Alexanderplatz in Berlin-Mitte, the tower was constructed between 1965–69 by the government of the German Democratic Republic (GDR). It was intended to be both a symbol of Communist power and of Berlin. It remains the latter today, as it is easily visible throughout the central and some suburban districts of Berlin. With its height of 368 metres (including antenna) it is the tallest structure in Germany, and the second-tallest structure in the European Union. Of three tallest structures in Europe, it is 0.5m shorter than the Riga Radio and TV Tower, and 8m taller than the Trbovlje Power Station in 2017. The structure is also more than 220 meters higher than the old Berlin Radio Tower in the western part of the city, which was built in the 1920s.</string>
    <string name="spots_places_brandenburg_desc">The Brandenburg Gate is an 18th-century neoclassical monument in Berlin, built on the orders of Prussian king Frederick William II after the (temporarily) successful restoration of order during the early Batavian Revolution. One of the best-known landmarks of Germany, it was built on the site of a former city gate that marked the start of the road from Berlin to the town of Brandenburg an der Havel, which used to be capital of the Margraviate of Brandenburg.</string>
    <string name="spots_places_gendarmenmarkt_desc">The Gendarmenmarkt is a square in Berlin and the site of an architectural ensemble including the Konzerthaus (concert hall) and the French and German Churches. In the centre of the square stands a monumental statue of Germany\'s renowned poet Friedrich Schiller. The square was created by Johann Arnold Nering at the end of the seventeenth century as the Linden-Markt and reconstructed by Georg Christian Unger in 1773. The Gendarmenmarkt is named after the cuirassier regiment Gens d'Armes, which had stables at the square until 1773.</string>


    <string name="food_drink_schokoladenhaus_desc">The Rausch Schokoladenhaus, located in the Gendarmenmarkt square in Berlin’s Mitte district, is completely devoted to enjoyment. Leave all of your cares outside and let yourself be enchanted by the unique world of chocolate. Just step inside.</string>
    <string name="food_drink_marjellchen_desc">Specialties from East Prussia, West Prussia, Pomerania, Silesia and elsewhere…</string>
    <string name="food_drink_losteria_desc">Once the doors open at L’Osteria, you’ll feel like you’re in a typical Italian osteria, where people get together to eat really well and enjoy the company of families, friends, couples, old and young. It is a lively atmosphere, and the delicious smell of authentic Italian cuisine lingers in the air. This is an open, welcoming place, where everyone can be themselves and feel at home. L’Osteria is famous for the best, best pizza and pasta d’amore. The sizeable pizza is larger than the plate. It is frequently ordered by two persons with different toppings on each half. And wait until you see the pasta!</string>
    <string name="food_drink_jolly_desc">The restaurant is furnished in a modern asian style. From our terrace you can enjoy the lovely view to the Museumsinsel. Our chef will prepare the food in our open kitchen for everyone to see. Jolly offers authentic Asian cuisine. We prepare every meal with fresh ingredients and lots of love. The Asian cuisine is famous for its varied flavours. We look forward to your visit.</string>
    <string name="food_drink_ristoranteamano_desc">Ristorante a Mano opened the doors in 2011. After a short time the restaurant established to a high recommended location with one of the best italian cuisine in Berlin. Some reasons are exquisite, daily changing dishes and a distinctive mediterranean flair.</string>

    <string name="test1">The Ritz-Carlton</string>
    <string name="test2">Located in the heart of Berlin, on prestigious Potsdamer Platz, within walking distance to the Sony Center, The Ritz Carlton, Berlin provides an amazing location for discovery. Our luxury hotel in Berlin, Germany is close to renowned shopping galleries, the Brandenburg Gate, the Diplomatic and Government District and the heart of cultural Berlin.</string>
</resources>
